<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>.:: Visual Partner-Ship ::.</title>
    <link>https://visualpartnership.xyz/</link>
    <description>Recent content on .:: Visual Partner-Ship ::.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2021 20:46:08 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://visualpartnership.xyz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Preguntas Frecuentes y Referencias</title>
      <link>https://visualpartnership.xyz/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2021 20:46:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://visualpartnership.xyz/faq/</guid>
      <description>¿Qué me recomiendas para practicar y seguir mejorando? Recuerda que esto es un camino de disciplina y esfuerzo, así que practica y practica todos los días que te sean posible, pule tu trazo, y úsalo en tu día a día. Seguramente así llegará un punto donde necesites más ayuda para encontrar tu camino, así que te aconsejo seguir a otras personas de este mundo del Visual Thinking, busca los hashtags #VisualThinking #PensamientoVisual para que encuentres más referencias, y anímate a preguntar, la comunidad es muy generosa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Código de Conducta</title>
      <link>https://visualpartnership.xyz/codeofconduct/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2021 20:43:57 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://visualpartnership.xyz/codeofconduct/</guid>
      <description>En Visual Partner-Ship 💖 consideramos que el aprendizaje debe de darse en un entorno de respeto, confianza y seguridad.
Nuestros valores 🏆
 Respeto: escuchar con empatía, crear espacios de comunicación basada en el respeto. Considera las diferentes opiniones, interpretaciones, evitando hacer juicios de valor Consideración: las personas podemos tener diferentes contextos. Piensa en cómo los otros interpretan tus palabras, la comunicación requiere un esfuerzo importante. Apertura y curiosidad: Asume las buenas intenciones por parte de los demás participantes, enfócate en aprender y compartir.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Use Snap to install the Hugo edge version on Fedora and Ubuntu</title>
      <link>https://visualpartnership.xyz/use-snap-to-install-the-hugo-edge-version-on-fedora-and-ubuntu/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 12:59:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://visualpartnership.xyz/use-snap-to-install-the-hugo-edge-version-on-fedora-and-ubuntu/</guid>
      <description>If you are using the Fedora or Ubuntu Linux distributions &amp;ndash; I&amp;rsquo;m currently on Fedora 28 &amp;ndash; and would like to help test the latest development version of Hugo, or if you just want to be on the bleeding-edge of things, this post is for you.
Fedora-only steps To get started, install Snap on Fedora:
sudo dnf install snapd Add the Snap directory to your PATH by adding this line to your ~/.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Script to add a page-level variable to content front matter in hugo</title>
      <link>https://visualpartnership.xyz/script-to-add-a-page-level-variable-to-content-front-matter-in-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 12:43:20 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://visualpartnership.xyz/script-to-add-a-page-level-variable-to-content-front-matter-in-hugo/</guid>
      <description>This was originally a question posed on the hugo discussion forums.
The user wanted to loop through all her content files and add a weight page-level variable to the front matter. The value of weight needed to be the first 2 characters of the content filename, since her content was named like 01_content.md, 02_content.md, etc.
She then wanted to range through her pages by their weight, like so:
{{ range .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating a New Theme</title>
      <link>https://visualpartnership.xyz/creating-a-new-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://visualpartnership.xyz/creating-a-new-theme/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This tutorial will show you how to create a simple theme in Hugo. I assume that you are familiar with HTML, the bash command line, and that you are comfortable using Markdown to format content. I&amp;rsquo;ll explain how Hugo uses templates and how you can organize your templates to create a theme. I won&amp;rsquo;t cover using CSS to style your theme.
We&amp;rsquo;ll start with creating a new site with a very basic template.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://visualpartnership.xyz/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://visualpartnership.xyz/about/</guid>
      <description>This Theme Thanks for visiting this theme demo. If you&amp;rsquo;re interested, checkout my other stuff over at https://zwbetz.com
Hugo Hugo is the world’s fastest framework for building websites. It is written in Go.
It makes use of a variety of open source projects including:
 https://github.com/russross/blackfriday https://github.com/alecthomas/chroma https://github.com/muesli/smartcrop https://github.com/spf13/cobra https://github.com/spf13/viper  Learn more and contribute on GitHub.
  _Favicon made by [Freepik](https://www.freepik.com/), from [Flaticon](https://www.flaticon.com/), licensed by [CC 3.0](http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by/3.0/)._  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>(Hu)go Template Primer</title>
      <link>https://visualpartnership.xyz/goisforlovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://visualpartnership.xyz/goisforlovers/</guid>
      <description>Hugo uses the excellent Go html/template library for its template engine. It is an extremely lightweight engine that provides a very small amount of logic. In our experience that it is just the right amount of logic to be able to create a good static website. If you have used other template systems from different languages or frameworks you will find a lot of similarities in Go templates.
This document is a brief primer on using Go templates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started with Hugo</title>
      <link>https://visualpartnership.xyz/hugoisforlovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://visualpartnership.xyz/hugoisforlovers/</guid>
      <description>Step 1. Install Hugo Go to Hugo releases and download the appropriate version for your OS and architecture.
Save it somewhere specific as we will be using it in the next step.
More complete instructions are available at Install Hugo
Step 2. Build the Docs Hugo has its own example site which happens to also be the documentation site you are reading right now.
Follow the following steps:
 Clone the Hugo repository Go into the repo Run hugo in server mode and build the docs Open your browser to http://localhost:1313  Corresponding pseudo commands:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Migrate to Hugo from Jekyll</title>
      <link>https://visualpartnership.xyz/migrate-from-jekyll/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://visualpartnership.xyz/migrate-from-jekyll/</guid>
      <description>Move static content to static Jekyll has a rule that any directory not starting with _ will be copied as-is to the _site output. Hugo keeps all static content under static. You should therefore move it all there. With Jekyll, something that looked like
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ images/ logo.png  should become
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ static/ ▾ images/ logo.png  Additionally, you&amp;rsquo;ll want any files that should reside at the root (such as CNAME) to be moved to static.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
